Alexander McComb

Front End Engineer

128 Allison Circle Anderson, SC 29625 (434) 242-7255 alexanderjmccomb@gmail.com

SKILLS

Worked on many projects using HTML5 CSS3(Sass as a preprocessor) and JavaScript. With projects I built applications using React JS alongside with Backbone. Familiar with using Jquery and other libraries such as underscore. Used Git and GitHub to put my projects under source control and used gh-pages for hosting and deploying my projects. Have familiarity with Heroku for hosting a few applications.

EXPERIENCE

WALB TV NBC/ABC, Albany GA - Morning Show Teleprompter

August 2014 - February 2015

- Ran the teleprompter for the morning anchors and weatherman.
- Controlled cameras and other equipment for live production.

United States Marine Corps, Iwakuni, Japan - Aviation Ordnance System Technician

June 2010 - June 2014

- Maintained over \$300 million worth of ammunition and explosives.
- Coordinated daily inspections and deliveries of ammunition and explosives.
- Contacted units and other departments for coordinating times for picking up and returning ammunition and explosives.
- Managed all document record and issuing.

Advance Auto Parts, Charlottesville VA - Sales Representative

January 2009 - May 2010

- Maintained inventory stock and presentation.
- Helped customers find products for the vehicle.
- Assisted customers with installing car batteries, head lights, and windshield wipers.

EDUCATION

The Iron Yard - Greenville, SC - Certificate of Completion

September 2016- December 2016

Full Sail University Online - Orlando, FL

May 2015- August 2016

Fluvanna County High School - Palmyra, VA - High School Diploma

September 2004 - May 2008